In the last programming video,
在上一个编程视频中
you saw how we could simulate draws from the null hypothesis,
你学习了如何用零假设模拟抽样
and that if our statistic was in the bulk of the distribution,
如果统计量处于分布区域内
this suggested that the statistic was likely from that null.
这表明统计量可能来自这个零假设
However, if the statistic was farther out from the bulk of the distribution,
但是 如果统计量远离分布区域
this suggested that the null wasn't likely to have generated our statistic.
这表明零假设不可能产生统计量
Then you saw that we can calculate p-values based on the shaded region starting at
你还学习了如何根据阴影区计算 p 值
the value of our observed statistic through the tail of the distribution,
阴影区从我们观察到的统计量开始 延伸到分布区域的尾部
where the shaded region is dependent on our alternative.
阴影区取决于对立假设
Based on the previous video,
在上一个视频中
you had simulated values of the sampling distribution from the null, like this.
你用零假设模拟了抽样分布的值 就像这样
Imagine that we have the alternative hypothesis
假设我们的对立假设是
that the population mean is greater than 70,
总体均值大于 70
then we could calculate the p-value as the proportion
我们可以将 p 值作为
of the simulated draws that are larger than our sample mean.
大于样本均值的模拟样本的比例来计算
Here, you can see that that would give us a p-value of one.
这里可以看出 我们得到的 p 值是一
Remember, large p-value suggests that we shouldn't move away from the null hypothesis.
记住 p 值较大表示不应该抛弃零假设
In this case, that suggests that we should stay with the mean being less than 70.
在这个案例中 这表明 我们应该认为均值小于 70
Here, we've calculated the null values that are greater than our sample mean.
这里 我们已经计算了大于样本均值的空值
Since this is one,
由于这是一
our p-value is large and therefore we wouldn't move away from the null hypothesis
p 值较大 因此 我们不会抛弃零假设
that suggests that our population mean is truly less than or equal to 70.
这表明总体均值实际小于等于 70
If our new null and alternative hypotheses look like this instead,
如果新的零假设和对立假设是这样
we would calculate our p-value a little differently.
计算 p 值的方法稍微有些不同
Here, because our alternative is less than 70,
这里 由于对立假设是小于 70
we would now look at the shaded region to the left of our statistic.
我们现在可以看统计量左边的阴影区域
This would change our p-value to the following.
p 值将变成这样
Now that our p-value is zero,
由于 p 值是零
this suggests that we reject the null hypothesis in favor of an alternative,
这表明我们应该抛弃零假设 选择对立假设
suggesting that the population mean is less than 70.
表明总体均值小于 70
So if this was our null and alternative hypothesis,
所以 如果这是零假设和对立假设
we would now want to look at the values that are more extreme
我们现在应该看 在远离零假设的任一方向
than our sample mean in either direction away from the null hypothesis.
都比样本均值极端的值
That looks like this equation here.
看起来像这个方程
Let's take a look at where these values fall on the above histogram.
我们看一下 在上面这个直方图中 这些值从哪里开始下降
You can see that if we were to shade more extreme than either of these regions,
可以看出 如果将这些区域两边的区域涂阴影
there are essentially no data points from
零假设中基本上没有
our null hypothesis that fall outside of this region.
处于这个区域之外的数据点了
Again, we would have evidence to suggest that
我们将找到证据证明
the null hypothesized value did not generate our sample statistic.
零假设值不会产生样本统计量